Mshari A. Dajam

2360, Jeddah. Saudi Arabia Phone: +966 548606667

email: mshari-705@hotmail.com

Work Experience

Administrative Assistant (Feb 2020 - Now)

Ali Abdullah BinDaiam EST.

Jeddah, Saudi Arabia

Scheduled meetings and coordinated appointments Mantained confidentiality and discretion Organized and sorted incoming mail Drafted documents, reports and memos Managed expenses and travel assigments

Recorded and transcribed meeting minutes

Data Entry Clerk (May 2018 – Jan 2020)

Bin Dajam LTD.

Updated company databases, inputting customer and supplier information, including contact information and payment details Validated data to ensure correct entry and accuracy, spotting errors and correcting mistakes as necessary

Coordinated with personnel in various departments to double-check the accuracy of dubious data entries

Maintained digital and hard copy filing systems, sorting incoming mail, labeling customer records, and reviewing files on an annual basis Handled delicate client information, including phone numbers, contact information, and income tax documents, with care and confidentiality Performed basic office tasks, including filing paperwork, printing documents, using copy and fax machines, and running errands

Education Jeddah University (2018 – now)

Software Engineering

Ali Abdullah BinDajam EST. Mr. Ali Dajam, General Manager Eng. Abdulmalik Dajam, CEO AliDajambindajam.com

Bin Dajam LTD. a.malikbindajamltd.com

Summary

Software Engineer enthusiastically for creating inventive projects that facilitate the proficiency and adequacy of authoritative achievement. Knowledgeable in innovation and composing code to make frameworks that are solid and easy to understand. A talented pioneer who has the demonstrated capacity to propel, instruct and deal with a group of experts to construct programming programs and really track changes. Certain communicators, vital scholars, and inventive makers foster programming that is redone to meet an organization's hierarchical necessities feature its center, and further its prosperity.

Professional Skills

Strong written and verbal communication skills Strong collaboration skills Core programming languages, Microservices development Adaptability Troubleshooting

Arabic, native English, advanced